<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-01T16:06:05+02:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Cooking</title><subtitle>Cooking easy &amp; fun</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Vegetarian pasta</title><link href="/2018/11/29/vegetarian-pasta.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vegetarian pasta" /><published>2018-11-29T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-29T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/2018/11/29/vegetarian-pasta</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/29/vegetarian-pasta.html">&lt;section class=&quot;dish vegetarian-pasta&quot;&gt;
    &lt;article&gt;
        &lt;h2&gt;Vegetarian pasta&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Italian cuisine is always very romantic. You will surprise your mate with this unique and easy recipe. Suitable for vegetarians and spaghetti lovers. This will be one of the best food you ever try.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;You need pasta, mushrooms and tomato sauce. Boil the paste for 10 minutes and add the remaining products. The fragrance will enchant your guests. The recipe is suitable for romantic dinners.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/article&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Vegetarian pasta Italian cuisine is always very romantic. You will surprise your mate with this unique and easy recipe. Suitable for vegetarians and spaghetti lovers. This will be one of the best food you ever try. You need pasta, mushrooms and tomato sauce. Boil the paste for 10 minutes and add the remaining products. The fragrance will enchant your guests. The recipe is suitable for romantic dinners.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/pasta.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Banana cake</title><link href="/2018/11/29/banana-cake.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Banana cake" /><published>2018-11-29T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-29T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/2018/11/29/banana-cake</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/29/banana-cake.html">&lt;section class=&quot;dish banana-cake&quot;&gt;
    &lt;article&gt;
        &lt;h2&gt;Banana cake&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Cake is easy to prepare and always gets good. We have reduced the amount of sugar in it to make it healthier and replace it with honey. Beat eggs to foam, add sugar and vanilla.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Pour the flour and put it in the mixture. Bake in the oven for about 30 minutes. Make yourself a banana sauce and chocolate banana. Once it has cooled down, mix it with the mixture.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/article&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Banana cake Cake is easy to prepare and always gets good. We have reduced the amount of sugar in it to make it healthier and replace it with honey. Beat eggs to foam, add sugar and vanilla. Pour the flour and put it in the mixture. Bake in the oven for about 30 minutes. Make yourself a banana sauce and chocolate banana. Once it has cooled down, mix it with the mixture.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/banana-cake.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Musaka</title><link href="/2018/11/29/musaka.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Musaka" /><published>2018-11-29T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-29T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/2018/11/29/musaka</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/29/musaka.html">&lt;section class=&quot;dish musaka&quot;&gt;
    &lt;article&gt;
        &lt;h2&gt;Musaka&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Musaka is a typical bulgarian dish. Here we have tried to keep up with the traditions of our grandmothers. When you consume it you will remember the aromat of your mother kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Cut the potatoes at retail and fry them together with onions and carrots. Put them in a tray in the oven for 20 minutes. Add a layer of eggs and milk. After another 10 minutes the musaka will be ready.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/article&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Musaka Musaka is a typical bulgarian dish. Here we have tried to keep up with the traditions of our grandmothers. When you consume it you will remember the aromat of your mother kitchen. Cut the potatoes at retail and fry them together with onions and carrots. Put them in a tray in the oven for 20 minutes. Add a layer of eggs and milk. After another 10 minutes the musaka will be ready.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/musaka.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Roasted mushrooms</title><link href="/2018/11/29/roasted-mushrooms.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Roasted mushrooms" /><published>2018-11-29T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-29T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/2018/11/29/roasted-mushrooms</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/29/roasted-mushrooms.html">&lt;section class=&quot;dish roasted-mushrooms&quot;&gt;
    &lt;article&gt;
        &lt;h2&gt;Roasted mushrooms&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;In the recipe are used mushrooms in the forest. Their aroma will make the entree unique and enrich it with flavonoids. They are very healthy.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Choose healthy sponge mushrooms. Wash them well and cut them into large pieces. Put them in hot water for 15 minutes. Then fry them in oil until golden. Add parsley and salt. Serve as an appetizer.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/article&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Roasted mushrooms In the recipe are used mushrooms in the forest. Their aroma will make the entree unique and enrich it with flavonoids. They are very healthy. Choose healthy sponge mushrooms. Wash them well and cut them into large pieces. Put them in hot water for 15 minutes. Then fry them in oil until golden. Add parsley and salt. Serve as an appetizer.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/roasted-vegetable-food-mushrooms.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Skebe corba</title><link href="/2018/11/29/skebe-corba.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Skebe corba" /><published>2018-11-29T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-29T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/2018/11/29/skebe-corba</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/29/skebe-corba.html">&lt;section class=&quot;dish skebe-corba&quot;&gt;
    &lt;article&gt;
        &lt;h2&gt;Skebe corba&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The dish is asian and combines the tastes of Mediterranean food and the most used Eastern spices. Prepare for 20 minutes and will fascinate you with its Asian flavor.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Use small fish cleaned from the bones. Add onions, carrots and celery. Cook for 20 minutes. Serve warm in a suitable dish.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/article&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Skebe corba The dish is asian and combines the tastes of Mediterranean food and the most used Eastern spices. Prepare for 20 minutes and will fascinate you with its Asian flavor. Use small fish cleaned from the bones. Add onions, carrots and celery. Cook for 20 minutes. Serve warm in a suitable dish.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/soup.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Tomato soup</title><link href="/2018/11/29/tomato-soup.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tomato soup" /><published>2018-11-29T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-29T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>/2018/11/29/tomato-soup</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/29/tomato-soup.html">&lt;section class=&quot;dish tomato-soup&quot;&gt;
    &lt;article&gt;
        &lt;h2&gt;Tomato soup&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;This soup is suitable for hot summer days, so it can be consumed cold. The variety of tomatoes in the recipe can be replaced by your choice.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Brush and cut well ripe tomatoes, put them in hot water. Add spices like parsley and red pepper. Suitable for hot and cold consumption.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/article&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Tomato soup This soup is suitable for hot summer days, so it can be consumed cold. The variety of tomatoes in the recipe can be replaced by your choice. Brush and cut well ripe tomatoes, put them in hot water. Add spices like parsley and red pepper. Suitable for hot and cold consumption.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/tomato-soup.jpg" /></entry></feed>